<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tools on Hello Friend</title>
    <link>https://xuanyang-cn.github.io/categories/tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tools on Hello Friend</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 18:30:27 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xuanyang-cn.github.io/categories/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How To Build Develop Environment with Vim</title>
      <link>https://xuanyang-cn.github.io/posts/2022/11/how-to-build-develop-environment-with-vim/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 18:30:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanyang-cn.github.io/posts/2022/11/how-to-build-develop-environment-with-vim/</guid>
      <description>This article helps myself to quickly establish a workable environments in Ubuntu with vim for
 The following languages: Golang, Python, CPP, MarkDown. Auto completion, jump to definition, rename variables, jump to files, jump to greps, auto lint Shell tools: git, rg, hugo, etc.  Just use docker  Download docker Use Dockerfile  I have a really Ubuntu 1. Install essentials Maybe important $ sudp apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; apt install wget curl ca-certificates build-essential gnupg2 lcov libtool m4 autoconf automake libssl-dev zlib1g-dev libboost-all-dev libboost-program-options-dev libboost-system-dev libboost-filesystem-dev libboost-serialization-dev libboost-python-dev libboost-regex-dev libcurl4-openssl-dev libtbb-dev libzstd-dev libaio-dev uuid-dev libpulse-dev netcat iputils-ping liblapack3 libblas-dev liblapack-dev Very important $ sudo apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; apt install g++ gcc gfortran git make ccache python3 python3-dev python3-pip gdb gdbserver htop tig zsh vim language-pack-en xmodmap hugo ripgrep global universal-ctags terminator $ sudo apt remove --purge -y &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo rm -rf /var/lib/apt/lists/* # install CMake $ wget -qO- &amp;#34;https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
